UZEEL UR REHMAN

WEB DEVELOPER/DIGITAL MARKETING/GRAPHIC DESIGNER/PROJECT MANAGER/SALES

I am keen to learn new things in life and as part of my early career, I am willing to put my hands everywhere I can so I can learn more, I am sure things appear difficult than they are, I am a firm believer in my ability to adapt to new changes and would love to improve myself all roundly so one day I can connect all my dots together and use them to reach my desired destination.



ABOUT ME

Digital Marketing ninja with a demonstrated experienced corroboration of working in the fintech industry. Skilled in Frontend Development, Digital Marketing, and User Experience (UX). KWOE freshly of sales, over 27 months of experience in building and managing a startup, I am still young and optimistic about my bright & successful career in the making.

CONTACT INFORMATION

+971-568916665 Dubai, UAE

> +92-3496634951 Lahore, Pakistan

- uzeelmegmail.com www.uzeel.ml
- in LinkedIn: @UzeelUrRehman

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Raffles World Academy

INTERNATIONAL BACCALAUREATE - 2017-2018

- Finished my high school from raffles world Academy.
- being passionate for sports, enabled me to win many gold medals and a the first division top place trophy with the football team.
- Finished 300 CAS hours of service & internships as a requirement of IB

WORK EXPERIENCE

Strategic Initiatives - Tech & Digital Marketing

FINMAAL.COM AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT (2 YEARS 11 MONTHS) DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES

- 1. FINMAAL with its multiple business verticals is on a mission to simplify financial products for making people's lives easier.
- 2. Marketplace: Online access to financial products in a simplified manner.
- 3. Data Science: helping companies making sense out of their data
- 4. Market Intelligence: Insightful data in graphical representation
- 5. Financial Products Manufacturing & Licensing: Customercentric yet profit-
- 6. oriented products for Fls
- 7. Digital solutions for financial Institutions: Data Analytics, marketplace &
- 8. automation

Marketing Lead - Dubai

AIESEC FEBRUARY 2020 - PRESENT U.A.E , DUBAI

An international youth-run, not-for-profit organization that provides youth with leadership development, cross-cultural internships, and global volunteer exchange experiences. The organization focuses on empowering young people to make a Progressive social impact. Analyze the NGO situation on marketing and finances. Work with social engagement. Getting in sign-ups with organizations. Business and coverage along with handling relations with them. Handle campaigns. Team management.

Founder & CEO

FAAQI.COM AUGUST 2017 - MARCH 2018 U.A.E , DUBAI

 E-commerce Store Faaqi.com, Selling goods and shipping them to your doorstep. I set up my online e-commerce store back in my 10th grade of high school, I managed all the social media pages, the customer interaction and the platform in general which I made from Shopify. I stopped as I had to shift my focus in my studies.

Marketing & PR

PAKISTAN YOUTH FORUM | DUBAI EXECUTIVE BOARD MEMBER - JOINT SECRETARY MARCH 2021 - PRESENT DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES

 As joint secretary of PYF, i have the responsibility to handle and take care of all sorts of Accounting/Finance & Exectuvive Generial/Chairperson work. Responsible fro any s decision making.

Marketing & PR

PAKISTAN YOUTH FORUM | DUBAI COMMITTEE MEMBER - MEDIA TEAM / WEB DEVELOPMENT AND MARKETING FEBRUARY 2020 - MARCH 2021 DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES

Part of the PYF as a Tech Volunteer. Being part of PYF and
my role in it enables me to connect with like-minded people
who want to give back to the community with their ambitions
and skillsets. I believe the only success that matters is how
important and what difference you made in your life and the
people around you.

Interne - Media team & Backstage laison

STEP CONFERENCE
MEDIA AND BACKSTAGE - LAISON
FEBRUARY 2019 - FEBRUARY 2019
DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES

Volunteered to help to organize and being part of a well-known event here in Dubai, with many well-known personalities and important discussions related to my career path, I decided to be part of STEP 2019 in making it a success as well as getting to experience the "behind the scenes" of what goes behind the stage, I also attended a few workshops and met some great personalities myself. I managed to connect with people I've met in the past and managed to make a few new friends as well. It was a great experience all together.